I wonder
what Wang Jiming's last words were.
9 p.m.
The old house of the Lin family.
Go alone.
No waiting after the time.
The truth will be buried forever.
[The number you dialed is temporarily unavailable.]
[Sorry,]
[the number you dialed is temporarily unavailable.]
The last sentence.
Did Jiming not die on the spot?
Then what did he leave behind?
The bait has been set.
Now we'll see if the fish
are greedy enough.
Yu,
are you home?
I'm coming to you.
Let's go over the clues again.
I'm not feeling well.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Not feeling well?
What's wrong?
Do you need me to come over?
I'm fine.
I just have a headache.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
How dare you call me?
Jiming,
go to the ancestral house now.
Ms. Wen
asked me to prepare something
and went to the ancestral house alone.
I heard her talking
on the phone
with Lawyer Guan.
I'm afraid...
What?
I'm afraid something bad is going to happen.
When did she go there?
Not long ago.
Coming.
Please have some tea.
Director Wen, you went to great lengths to invite me here.
It's not just for a simple tea, right?
What did Jiming say in the end?
Sit.
Don't be afraid.
It's just the two of us.
I just want
to talk to you alone.
After all, only the two of us
know what happened before,
don't we?
Gu Qingyu,
just say it.
Take your time.
Have some tea first
to soothe your throat.
This is the Pu'er tea
Mu Yun loved the most.
It's a pity
he can't drink it anymore.
What?
Are you afraid I'll poison you?
Wang Jiming
was in great pain.
Before the explosion,
he seemed to have foreseen something.
He said
he regretted it.
What did he regret?
He regretted
marrying you.
The tea is drunk.
You can go now.
You can't go.
You don't look well.
This old house is too damp.
You shouldn't stay here too long.
Goodbye.
You...
My cup!
Xintian.
Doctor,
how is she?
She is suffering from food poisoning,
accompanied by signs of acute kidney failure.
The situation is very dangerous.
Fortunately, she was brought here in time.
We are doing our best to save her.
What did she eat?
I don't know.
Gastric lavage,
dialysis, and medication.
We need the patient's family to sign.
Okay.
I'll sign.
Doctor,
please,
you must save her.
We'll do our best.
You're awake.
How do you feel?
The doctor told me
you had severe food poisoning.
What did you eat yesterday?
I don't
know.
Maybe it's because of the takeout.
Takeout?
How can it cause acute kidney failure?
Yu,
are you hiding something from me?
Who sent me here?
Lin Jiming.
He contacted me.
Where is he?
I'm really fine.
I'm just a bit tired.
I need to rest a bit more.
Alright.
Then get some rest.
Where did she go last night?
Where exactly did you find her?
Stop asking.
She doesn't want to talk about it right now.
Lin Jiming.
This wasn't an accident.
I know.
Let her decide for herself.
She's been through enough.
Tiantian.
Are you okay?
You look pale.
I'm fine.
Go ahead.
Well,
my brother helped me.
So we found that
Wen Shiyi is very quick,
but not quick enough.
In the past 72 hours,
she transferred at least 530 million yuan
through seven overseas shell companies.
The money was finally transferred to South America.
The account holder is
Qi Zhou.
Zhou Qi.
So he's hiding in South America.
And there's something more crucial.
I've traced back
the IP address used
when she executed these transactions.
The source is in this city.
Binhai District.
Abandoned pier.
So,
she's alive.
Yes.
She was saved.
Zhan Shan
Get ready.
It's time to go.